hackspirit.com 2019-04-21

# Privacy Policy - Hack Spirit

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us at Hack Spirit (“HS” or “we”). We know that you care about the use of your personal information and how it is shared. Because of this, we will not use or share your information except as provided in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect about you on our website, how we use such information, and the safeguards we have in place to reduce the risk of unauthorized access and use.

Please carefully read this Privacy Policy, which is part of our Terms of Use, before using our website, DailyWire.com, ForwardPublishing.com, and any related HS webpages or mobile sites. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, please do not to use our website. By accessing or using our website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Contents**

  * Contact Information
  * Scope of this Privacy Policy
  * Information We Collect
  * Cookies and Online Tracking Technologies
  * How We Use the Information We Collect
  * Sharing Your Information
  * Opt-out Procedures
  * Your California Privacy Rights
  * Information Security
  * Credit Card Information
  * Accessing and Correcting Your Information
  * Transfer of Information to the United States
  * Information About Children
  * Links to Other Materials
  * Changes to Our Privacy Policy

**Contact Information**

Should you have any questions about our website or this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Hack Spirit  
ATTN: Customer Service  
42D Melrose St  
Parkdale, VIC 3195  
Australia

OR our [online form](https://hackspirit.com/contact)

**Scope of this Privacy Policy**

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On this website (hackspirit.com) and related HS webpages (collectively, the “Site”).
  * In email, text and other electronic messages between you and the Site.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * Us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by any third party (including, if applicable, our affiliates and subsidiaries).
  * Any third party (including, if applicable, our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Site.

**Information We Collect**

Personal Information

As you use the Site, HS may ask you for certain personal information, including, but not limited to, your name, email address, postal address, and telephone number. Such information is provided voluntarily by you. In general, you can visit the Site without telling us who you are or providing any of the above personal information about yourself; however, you must provide personal information in order to subscribe to HS email alerts or register with the Site.

When you subscribe to HS’s paid content and set up an account, we also may ask you for additional information to complete the transaction and register you for the paid content, including, without limitation, your name, birthdate, mailing and billing address, zip code, phone number, email address, and credit card information.

Non-Personal Information

Additionally, HS and our advertising partners may use automatic data collection technologies such as cookies to collect non-personally identifiable information when you visit the Site, including, but not limited to, the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, your IP address, aggregate data about the number of visits to the Site, and aggregate data about the pages visited.  **HS and our advertising partners may use this information and connect this information with your personal information such as your name or email address to identify you and provide you with content that may be relevant to you.**

**Cookies and Online Tracking Technologies**

Like many websites, HS uses cookies and other tracking technologies to collect general, non-personally identifiable information about Site visitors. A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. HS uses cookies and other tracking technologies in order to improve the Site by providing aggregate information on the number of visitors and usage patterns, to allow us to recognize you when you revisit the Site to provide you with customized information and to remember your preferences, and to provide you with information that may be relevant to you from HS or our advertising partners.

HS may collect user personally identifiable information over time and across third-party websites, and we may permit third parties to gather information passively on the Site for behavioral advertising purposes.

We utilize third-party advertising companies to place advertisements on our website. These companies may implement cookies and other online tracking technologies to determine information about your visits to this website to determine what advertisements to show you.

You can control many tracking tools, including cookies, from your browser. In particular, you may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of the Site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to the Site.

Do Not Track Disclosure

Additionally, some Internet browsers have a ‘do not track’ feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. We are currently not set up to respond to such signals.

**How We Use the Information We Collect**

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
  * To provide you with notices about your transactions or communications with us.
  * To provide you with information that may be relevant to you from us or our advertising partners.
  * To allow our advertising partners to provide you with information that may be relevant to you.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
  * To present the Site and its contents to you.
  * To notify you about changes to the Site or any products or services we offer or provide through it.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on the Site.
  * For internal business operations, including the improvement of our products and services, data analytics and other normal business activities.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about products and services from HS and from our business partners that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please use the opt-out procedures described in the Opt-Out Procedures section.

**Sharing Your Information**

HS does not sell, trade, or disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties except as set forth herein.

We will only disclose personally identifiable information that we collect or you provide as described in this Privacy Policy:

  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, change in control, or other sale, transfer, or other action with respect to of some or all of HS assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, dissolution, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personally identifiable information held by HS about the Site users is among the assets affected.
  * To our affiliates and advertising partners to provide you with information that may be relevant to you, including for their own marketing purposes.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our [Terms of Use](https://hackspirit.com/terms-of-use) and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of HS, our customers, or others.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * To third party advertising companies to provide targeted advertisements on the Site.

With your consent. We may disclose aggregated, non-personally identifiable information about the Site users without restriction.

**Opt-Out Procedures**

If you do not wish to have your contact information shared by HS to third parties to promote their products or services, you can opt out by contacting us [here](https://hackspirit.com/contact).

If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be omitted from future promotional email distributions. This opt-out does not apply to transactional emails regarding your transactions or updates to our policies.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Under California law, a California resident with whom HS has an established relationship has the right to request certain information with respect to any personal information HS may have shared with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, HS may provide a cost-free means to opt out of such sharing.

HS has opted to provide you with a cost-free means to opt out of such sharing. If you do not want HS to disclose your personal information to other companies for their marketing purposes, please follow the opt-out procedures set forth above.

You may also send an email [here](https://hackspirit.com/contact) instructing us to no longer share your personal information with third parties who will use it for their direct marketing purposes. Please also include your name and all of the postal addresses and email addresses that you have provided to us.

**Information Security**

HS has implemented certain procedural, technical and physical security measures to help protect against the risk of loss, misuse, and alteration of sensitive information that you provide. We require third parties with whom we share personally identifiable information to do the same. Nevertheless, such security measures may not prevent all loss, misuse, or alteration of information on the Site, and HS is not responsible for any damages or liabilities relating to any such security failures. By using the Site, you understand that there is a risk that data and communications, including email and other electronic communications, may be accessed by unauthorized third parties. The foregoing does not affect any liability that cannot be excluded or limited under applicable law.

**Credit Card Information**

HS does not store your credit card information when you subscribe to our services. HS partners with third party providers to process credit card transactions.

**Accessing and Correcting Your Information**

HS email subscribers may review or modify their contact information on file by accessing their account online. Subscribers of paid content may also review or modify their contact information on file by accessing their account online. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

**Transfer of Information to the United States**

The Site is operated in the United States and is intended for users located in the United States. If you are located outside the United States, please be aware that information we collect, including personal information, may be transferred to, processed, and stored in the United States. By using the Site or providing us with any information, you consent to the transfer, processing, and storage of your information in the United States. You are also consenting to the application of United States federal and Texas state law in all matters concerning the Site and this Privacy Policy.

**Information About Children**

The Site is not directed to children under the age of 18 years. We will not request personally identifiable information from anyone whom we know to be under the age of 18. By using the Site, you represent and warrant that you are at least 18 years old. If we become aware that a customer is under the age of 18 and has registered or otherwise provided personally identifiable information, we will cancel the corresponding registration and remove his or her personally identifiable information.

**Links to Other Materials**

Sites may be linked to and from the Site that are not under the control of HS and HS shall have no responsibility or liability for the content or privacy practices of any such linked site or any link or linking program at any time. If you click on a link on the Site and link to a third party’s website, then this Privacy Policy will not apply to your personally identifiable information collected on that third party’s website and you must read the privacy policy on that website to see how your information will be handled.

Social media widgets or tools may appear on the Site. Your use of these widgets or tools will be governed by the terms of use and privacy policy of the applicable social media provider (e.g. Facebook®, YouTube®).

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our privacy practices. If we make any material changes, we may notify you by contacting you using the contact information that you have provided to us or by posting a notice on the Site – or by some combination of these methods. You agree to review the Privacy Policy posted to the Site each time you visit for the latest information on our privacy practices.

If you do not agree to any modifications to this Privacy Policy, your sole recourse is to immediately stop all use of the Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of any modifications to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. Please note that none of our employees or agents has the authority to vary any of our Policies.
